kabiza.com 2019-05-31

# Kabiza Wilderness Safaris -Our Privacy Policy for Clients-Site Visitors

## Your Information is Secure with us

### The Kabiza Wilderness Safaris – Privacy Policy means you are secure using our Site

* * *

**[](https://kabiza.com/kabiza-wilderness-safaris/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/kabiza-private-safari-tours-box-round-22.png)The ** **Kabiza Wilderness Safaris – Privacy Policy – Before we get into the legalese of Privacy.   We only find out anything about you when you contact us about a Primate or Wildlife Safari in Uganda or Rwanda. The information you submit to us via a contact form is removed from the Website Server and is only on given to the Safari Sales Department in our office. ** **We will never initiate any contact with you unless you contact us first and request more information. No information is shared with a third party with the exception of Gorilla or Chimpanzee Permits where we have to use your passport information but no email is given to Uganda Wildlife Authority except our own.   The same applies to lodges where we only give your name only to a lodge and the reservation is in Kabiza Wilderness Safaris name.  We value our personal privacy and we respect yours  – the reality Facebook, and Google know a lot more about you than**

**The Kabiza Wilderness Safaris – Privacy Policy also means that we never handle any credit card information when you make a payment, that is done through PesaPal – our  site has no Payment Page for your protection.**

### Kabiza Wilderness Safari  – Privacy Policy

Kabiza Wilderness Safaris – Privacy Policy -Kabiza Wilderness Safaris is committed to providing a safe and secure web site for people of all ages. We are dedicated to safeguarding all personal information collected online and to helping our visitors learn how to exercise control over personal information while exploring the Internet.

To help ensure a rewarding online experience for all visitors, we provide this summary of our information practices.

As we continue to offer different types of content and services, we may modify our practices from time to time. However, we will treat all personal information we collect in accordance with the privacy notice in effect at the time the information is collected.

#### I. The Information We Collect

At Kabiza Wilderness Safaris we do not collect personally identifiable information unless our visitors voluntarily provide it to us. When visitors come to our site, we automatically collect some non-personally identifiable information such as the type of computer operating system (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and browser (e.g., Firefox, Chrome, Internet Explorer) being used, and the domain name of the Internet service provider.

#### II. How We Use the Information

We use visitors’ personal information for internal purposes only, such as sending information via regular or electronic mail. We may also use personal information to send important notifications or updates.

We never sell, rent, or otherwise share our visitors’ personal information with third parties. We will disclose information we maintain as required by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a specific law enforcement agency’s request.

We will not use or transfer personally identifiable information in ways that are materially different from the ones described above without also obtaining consent for any materially different uses.

#### III. Cookies

We use Google Analytics to see how our visitors use our site. The cookies from the analysis tool does not contain any personal user information. We cannot identify you or your computer. We anonymize all IP numbers, which means you cannot be identified in the information we gather for statistical analysis. The information created in these cookies when you use our site is sent to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.

#### Google Analytics stores information about

  * the time of your first visit to the site
  * the time of your most recent visit to the site
  * the time your current visit began
  * how many times you have visited this site
  * your browser identification
  * the route by which you came to this site.

#### Google Tag Manager stores information about

  * recurring visitors
  * how you navigate within our website

#### IV. Security

To safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures.

We are particularly sensitive to visitors’ security concerns regarding the use of credit cards to pay for a safari.  You can cannot pay for a safari through our site – Payment Invoices are sent you, paid via bank to bank transfers or PesaPal online on their site, no credit card information is seen by us, neither is it stored by us

#### V. Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding Kabiza Wilderness Safaris – Privacy Policy the  and/or practices, please contact us at the following e-mail address: **[Kabiza Wilderness Safaris](mailto:kabizawilderrnesssafaris@kabiza.com)**
